esprit-club.com 2017-11-21

# Esprit :: Company :: Legal :: Your privacy

## What kind of information do we collect from visitors, and how do we use it?

We do not collect any personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website. We automatically only receive and record the following information from your computer and browser: IP-address as well as software and hardware attributes. We monitor visitor traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the design and layout of the website and to plan for a better collection of our products and services. The information we monitor do not allow us to draw any conclusions from the identities of the visitors to our website.

## 2 What kind of information do we collect from members and e-mail subscribers, and how do we use it?

When you join as a member or offer your e-mail address to receive e-mails from us, we collect the following information: your name, e-mail address, gender, age and date of birth to identify and to communicate with you as one of our members. The supply of personal information by the members or intended members is entirely voluntary, though without sufficient details we may not be able to serve you fully as a member.

We use the information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfil your requests for services, improve our website and services, inform you about our news, updates and member privileges and contact you for general requests.

## Do you share information with others?

As far as legally permitted, we keep confidential all personally identifiable information you provide us. However, we do disclose your personal information under certain circumstances. These include making disclosure when we believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to:

a.

comply with the law;

b.

maintain or develop our website and our business;

c.

enforce or apply the terms of any of our agreements; or

d.

protect the rights, property or safety of this website, our users, or others.

We may team up with other companies to promote or provide products, services, contests or promotions only when we have your permission. Subject to safeguards, we and such other company may need to cross-check our databases to avoid duplication or to use the combined information to identify and organise future marketing and promotions.

You can tell us not to share your e-mail address and other personal data simply by sending an e-mail message “re: no sharing” to   
[hotline@esprit.com](mailto:hotline@esprit.com). Clicking the hotlink will activate the pop-up message box.

We do not share, sell or rent any information you provide us with.

## Facebook Social Plugins

## What about "cookies"?

Our Website uses social plug-ins (“plug-ins”) from the social network facebook.com, which is operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA (“Facebook”). These plug-ins are marked with a Facebook logo or the label “Facebook Social Plug-in”. 

Whenever you access a Web page on our Website that contains one of these plug-in, your browser establishes a direct link to Facebook’s servers. The plug-in content is transferred from Facebook directly to your browser, which integrates the content into the Web page.

Integrating the plug-in sends information to Facebook indicating that you have accessed the corresponding page on our Website. The Internet address of the Web page you visited (including your IP address) is transmitted to one of Facebook’s servers in the USA where it is saved. As a rule, it is also not possible for Facebook to identify you personally based on the dynamically assigned IP address your Internet provider saves while you surf the Web. Once it has been published on Facebook, this information is not processed further or forwarded to third parties, and it is anonymised after a period of three months, so that the information is no longer associated with any particular user. This does not apply when you visit our Website and are logged on to Facebook at the same time. In this case, Facebook can share information about your visit with your Facebook account. 

In the event that you interact with plug-ins, for example by pressing the “Like” button or submitting a comment, the corresponding information is transferred from your browser directly to Facebook and saved there.   
For information on the purpose and scope of the information shared and how Facebook uses this data along with your respective rights and managing your privacy settings, please refer to Facebook’s [Privacy Policy](http://facebook.com/policy.php).   
If you are a member of Facebook and do not wish to share information about your visit to our Website with Facebook, you will need to log off of Facebook before visiting our Website.

A “cookie” is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored in the hard drive of your computer. We use cookies to help us provide customisable services. 

Cookies do not damage your system or impair its function in any way. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our site and other websites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

## What about “links”?

This website may contain links to third-party websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any such sites. This statement of privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website. We advise you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

## How do we make sure your information is secure?

Protecting your information is a priority for us. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your on-line information. The SSL encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information on-line, we also do everything in our power to protect personally identifiable information off-line. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job to fulfil the services to our customers (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.

## Protection of children’s privacy?

We are concerned about the safety of children in their use of the Internet. We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. If we receive actual knowledge that a member is under the age of 13 and has registered without the permission of his or her parent or guardian, we will remove from our files all personally identifiable registration information about that child.

## How do I change or delete my information?

You have the right to request access to, correction or deletion of the information about you held by us. If you wish to access, correct or delete your personal information with us, please inform us by sending an e-mail message to [hotline@esprit.com](mailto:hotline@esprit.com). Clicking the hotlink will activate the pop-up message box.

## How do I remove my information from e-mail and postal mailing lists?

We want to communicate with you only if you wish to hear from us. If you would rather not receive marketing or promotional communication from us, please inform us by sending an e-mail message “re: off” to [hotline@esprit.com](mailto:hotline@esprit.com). Clicking the hotlink will activate the pop-up message box.

## Consent

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of your information by Esprit International. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under which circumstances we disclose it.

## In summary

We are committed to safeguard your privacy with us. We use the information we collect on-line to enhance and improve your experience of being served by us. The supply of personal information to us is entirely voluntary. We do not sell or rent your personal information to others. We want to communicate with you only if you wish to hear from us.

If you wish to get in touch with us via mail, please contact us at:  
ESPRIT International, LLP  
1370 Broadway, 16th Floor   
New York, New York 10018   
U.S.A.
